<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Codelab_1.03</string>
    <string name="article_title">Haugen prepares to testify before British Parliament</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Posted by Facebook</string>
    <string name="article">Facebook whistleblower Frances Haugen is set to testify Monday before the British Parliament, answering questions about the trove of tens of thousands of documents she says show how the company has tracked real-world damage it helped exacerbate.

        <b>The Facebook Papers</b> www.google.com, \n\n a collection of internal documents, has triggered a fresh round of global reporting on the social media giant, including an investigation by The Washington Post. Lawmakers had already launched probes into Facebook\’s conduct following a series of stories by the Wall Street Journal.

Facebook releases its quarterly earnings results later Monday and chief executive Mark Zuckerberg is expected to speak to investors, possibly addressing criticism brought on by the reporting. Facebook whistleblower Frances Haugen is set to testify Monday before the British Parliament, answering questions about the trove of tens of thousands of documents she says show how the company has tracked real-world damage it helped exacerbate.

\n\n<b>The Facebook Papers</b>, a collection of internal documents, has triggered a fresh round of global reporting on the social media giant, including an investigation by The Washington Post. Lawmakers had already launched probes into Facebook\’s conduct following a series of stories by the Wall Street Journal.

Facebook releases its quarterly earnings results later Monday and chief executive Mark Zuckerberg is expected to speak to investors, possibly addressing criticism brought on by the reporting.Facebook whistleblower Frances Haugen is set to testify Monday before the British Parliament, answering questions about the trove of tens of thousands of documents she says show how the company has tracked real-world damage it helped exacerbate.

\n\n<b>The Facebook Papers</b>, a collection of internal documents, has triggered a fresh round of global reporting on the social media giant, including an investigation by The Washington Post. Lawmakers had already launched probes into Facebook\’s conduct following a series of stories by the Wall Street Journal.

Facebook releases its quarterly earnings results later Monday and chief executive Mark Zuckerberg is expected to speak to investors, possibly addressing criticism brought on by the reporting. He may even change the company\’s name, according to a report.</string>
</resources>